{
    "subject": "resource/Newhaven_Harbour_railway_station",
    "predicate": "property/platforms",
    "object": "2",
    "human_readable": "Newhaven Harbour railway station has 2 platforms.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.931731104850769,
            "question": "Give the number of platforms at Newhaven Harbour railway station."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.907048225402832,
            "question": "Does Newhaven Harbour railway station have more than one platform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8876979351043701,
            "question": "How many platforms does Newhaven Harbour railway station have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8796279430389404,
            "question": "What is the number of platforms at Newhaven Harbour railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8578197956085205,
            "question": "Newhaven Harbour railway station has a specific number of platforms. What is that number?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8562282919883728,
            "question": "What is the platform count at Newhaven Harbour railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8239884376525879,
            "question": "If you were to visit Newhaven Harbour railway station, how many platforms would you find?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8188745975494385,
            "question": "Is Newhaven Harbour railway station a single-platform station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8167828321456909,
            "question": "Describe the layout of Newhaven Harbour railway station in terms of platforms."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593552231788635,
            "question": "What can you say about the size of Newhaven Harbour railway station based on its platform count?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Newhaven Harbour railway station has 2 platforms.",
            "html": "dbpedia_524_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe the layout of Newhaven Harbour railway station in terms of platforms.",
            "html": "dbpedia_524_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Newhaven Harbour railway station a single-platform station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_524_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to visit Newhaven Harbour railway station, how many platforms would you find?",
            "html": "dbpedia_524_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_524_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that there are two platforms at the Newhaven Harbour train station, which supports the statement that it has 2 platforms."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}